<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModPlus>
  <mprParametrization
    LocalName="Parametrization"
    Description="Fill element parameters with different strategies">
    <!-- todo remove after 3.3.6.0 start -->
    <t1>Minimize window contents</t1>
    <t2>Expand window contents</t2>
    <t3>Add new configuration</t3>
    <t4>Duplicate current configuration</t4>
    <t5>Remove current configuration</t5>
    <!-- todo remove after 3.3.6.0 end -->
    <t6>Enter configuration name</t6>
    <t7>Strategies</t7>
    <t8>Add strategy</t8>
    <t9>Duplicate strategy</t9>
    <t10>Remove strategy</t10>
    <t11>Rules</t11>
    <t12>Processing elements from linked files</t12>
    <t13>The parent elements will be collected from the linked files. For example, for the InMass strategy, these are Masses, for the InSolid strategy, they are solid elements, etc. Elements will be collected according to the categories specified in the corresponding column of rules</t13>
    <t14>Strategies that work with element geometry (such as InRoom, InSpace, InSolid, SolidTouch, etc.) are recommended to run on the active view! If you run in the entire document, the elements take geometry that does not take into account the connection with other elements, which can lead to incorrect results</t14>
    <t15>Enter strategy name</t15>
    <t16>Add new rule</t16>
    <t17>Remove selected rules</t17>
    <t18>Duplicate selected rules</t18>
    <t19>Renumber according to the position in the table</t19>
    <t20>Export current configuration</t20>
    <t21>Import strategies into current configuration</t21>
    <t23>Import rules into current strategy</t23>
    <t24>Export rules of current strategy</t24>
    <t25>Write empty result</t25>
    <t26>Write an empty result, obtained by calculating the expression, to the target parameter. For string parameters it is an empty string, for numeric parameters it is 0</t26>
    <t27>Take into account the case when comparing string values in conditions</t27>
    <t28>Tolerance used when comparing numerical values in conditions</t28>
    <t29>Insert function</t29>
    <t30>Formula preview</t30>
    <t31>Formula Editor</t31>
    <t32>Case sensitive</t32>
    <t33>Write empty</t33>
    <t34>Unique identifier of the strategy (do not change it!):</t34>
    <t35>Custom name of the strategy:</t35>
    <t36>copy</t36>
    <t37>Strategy</t37>
    <t38>no parameter</t38>
    <t39>Rule</t39>
    <t40>Expression</t40>
    <t41>SolidTouch: tolerance of the distance between faces, mm:</t41>
    <t42>Wrap text to new line</t42>
    <t43>Select or create configuration</t43>
    <t44>Algorithm for finding solids entries:</t44>
    <t45>Auxiliary Rays</t45>
    <t46>Boolean operations</t46>
    <t47>Sets the algorithm for finding solids entries for InRoom, InSpace, InMass, and InSolid strategies. The "Auxiliary Rays" algorithm works fast, but allows to determine if a solid belongs to only one parent solid. The "Boolean operations" algorithm works slow, but allows to determine if a solid belongs to more than one parent solid. See help for details</t47>
    <t48>Fields</t48>
    <t49>Favorite fields</t49>
    <t50>Add new field</t50>
    <t51>Remove field</t51>
    <t52>Insert field in formula</t52>
    <t53>Add fields from the list of favorite fields</t53>
    <t54>Add field to the list of favorite fields</t54>
    <t55>Remove field from the list of favorite fields</t55>
    <t56>The list of fields already contains a field with this key</t56>
    <t57>Duplicate field</t57>
    <t58>Mapping function names</t58>
    <t59>In this window, you can define your own names for the functions used in the formula editor. Function names must not contain spaces and control characters (brackets, commas, dots, etc.). Case is not important</t59>
    <t60>Search and replace</t60>
    <t61>Create field</t61>
    <t62>Enter a unique key for the new field</t62>
    <t63>Dissociate</t63>
    <t64>Remove the association of the target parameter with the global project parameter if there is an association</t64>
    <t65>Remove all strategies</t65>
    <t66>Copy selected rules to clipboard</t66>
    <t67>Paste rules from clipboard</t67>
    <t68>Update field value in all rules</t68>
    <t69>Show formula</t69>
    <t70>Hide formula</t70>
    <t71>Use the geometry of nested families if the family has no geometry</t71>
    <t72>Enter strategy description</t72>
    <t73>Decimal separator for numeric values:</t73>
    <t74>System</t74>
    <t75>The decimal separator for numeric values is used when converting numeric values to string values during formula calculation. Such conversions are performed when obtaining values from numeric parameters, when calculating mathematical expressions, and when calculating functions that result in numbers</t75>
    <t76>Number of rules: enabled/total</t76>
    <t77>Change the background of the strategy in the list</t77>
    <t78>Change the background of the first cell of the selected rules</t78>
    <t79>Parameterization results</t79>
    <t80>Configuration: {0}. Total number of strategies: {1}. Total number of rules: {2}. Total time spent: {3}</t80>
    <t81>Total number of processed elements</t81>
    <t82>Total execution time</t82>
    <t83>Rules executed:</t83>
    <t84>Number of elements that have been changed</t84>
    <t85>Number of elements that have been skipped</t85>
    <t86>Number of elements that could not be changed</t86>
    <t87>Processed elements</t87>
    <t88>Select all</t88>
    <t89>Isolate all</t89>
    <t90>Export to txt</t90>
    <t91>Table of Contents:</t91>
    <t93>Select the result of expression processing to see a list of processed element IDs</t93>
    <t94>Restricted mode</t94>
    <t95>If no filter is specified in the rule, a common strategy filter will be used</t95>
    <t96>Select views</t96>
    <t97>Data source</t97>
    <t98>Strategy filter</t98>
    <t99>Expand list of rules</t99>
    <t100>Collapse list of rules</t100>
    <t101>Select the source element in the model</t101>
    <t102>Expressions count:</t102>
    <t103>The following settings are saved in the current configuration</t103>
    <t104>Committing changes to the document:</t104>
    <t105>When setting value to parameter</t105>
    <t106>When processing rule</t106>
    <t107>When processing strategy</t107>
    <t108>When setting value to parameter - after setting each value to the parameter of each element, the changes in the document will be committed. In this case, in each subsequent formula expression you can use the values of the parameters changed in the previous formula expression. This option may require more time for processing.</t108>
    <t109>When processing rule - committing changes in the document will be performed after all expressions of one rule are processed. In this case it is not possible to change and then reuse the same parameter within one rule, because the changed parameter value is not yet committed in the document.</t109>
    <t110>When processing strategy - committing changes in the document will be performed after all strategy rules have been processed. In this case it is not possible to change and then reuse the same parameter in different rules of the same strategy, because the changed parameter value is not yet committed in the document.</t110>
    <t111>Export the current configuration. Use XML to store and transfer data. It is recommended to use Excel only for quick editing and subsequent loading back in</t111>
    <t112>Export the current strategy. Use XML to store and transfer data. It is recommended to use Excel only for quick editing and subsequent loading back in</t112>
    <msg1>Configuration will be deleted permanently! Are you sure you want to continue?</msg1>
    <msg2>Strategy will be deleted permanently! Are you sure you want to continue?</msg2>
    <msg3>List of strategies is not empty</msg3>
    <msg4>Replace current list of strategies or add imported strategies to list?</msg4>
    <msg5>Searching for relationships between element instances</msg5>
    <msg6>Processing strategy</msg6>
    <msg7>no elements were processed</msg7>
    <msg8>No elements were processed by the selected rules of the selected strategies</msg8>
    <msg9>Committing changes to a document...</msg9>
    <msg10>List of rules is not empty</msg10>
    <msg11>Replace current list of rules or add imported rules to list?</msg11>
    <msg12>Rule skipped because no formula is given</msg12>
    <msg13>Processing rule</msg13>
    <msg14>value setting is skipped, because the parameter "{0}" has the same value</msg14>
    <msg15>processed</msg15>
    <msg16>did not process with an error</msg16>
    <msg17>In a limited version of the plugin, you can create only one configuration</msg17>
    <msg18>In a limited version of the plugin, you can create up to three strategies</msg18>
    <msg19>In a limited version of the plugin, you can create up to three rules</msg19>
    <msg20>In the list of favorite fields there is already a field with this key</msg20>
    <msg21>Are you sure you want to irrevocably remove all strategies from the current configuration?</msg21>
    <msg22>The value of this field will be updated in all rules of all configurations when the field key matches.\nContinue?</msg22>
    <msg23>Field "{0}" updated: configuration "{1}" – strategy "{2}" – rule "{3}"</msg23>
    <msg24>Field "{0}" was not found in any rule!</msg24>
    <msg25>You cannot select elements in the current view. Switch to another view</msg25>
    <msg26>Replace the current strategy filters with the strategy filters from the imported file?</msg26>
    <msg27>Replace the current strategy data source with the data source from the imported file?</msg27>
    <msg28>The selected file is not a configuration storage file or a strategy storage file</msg28>
    <msg29>The selected file is not a strategy storage file</msg29>
    <msg30>A category added in a later Revit version and not present in the current Revit version has been removed from the "{0}" strategy filter for the source element</msg30>
    <msg31>A category added in a later Revit version and not present in the current Revit version has been removed from the "{0}" strategy filter for the target element</msg31>
    <msg32>A category added in a later Revit version and not present in the current Revit version has been removed from the rule "{0}" filter of the "{1}" strategy for the source element</msg32>
    <msg33>A category added in a later Revit version and not present in the current Revit version has been removed from the rule "{0}" filter of the "{1}" strategy for the target element</msg33>
    <err1>Each expression in a formula must start with the target parameter "$[ParameterName]="</err1>
    <err2>The number of opening round brackets must equal the number of closing ones</err2>
    <err3>The number of opening curly brackets must equal the number of closing ones</err3>
    <err4>Failed calculate an arithmetic expression</err4>
    <err5>Condition "{0}" must contain conditional comparison operators ({1})</err5>
    <!-- todo remove after 3.3.18.0 -->
    <err6>Condition "{0}" must contain values before and after "{1}"</err6>
    <err9>Unexpected conditional operator</err9>
    <err10>Failed to process the condition</err10>
    <err11>Function must contain numbers separated by a comma</err11>
    <err12>"{0}" is an invalid rounding convention. It is allowed to use "z" for AwayFromZero, or "e" for ToEven</err12>
    <err13>The number of fractional digits must be specified as an integer above 0 or as a fractional number from 0 to 1</err13>
    <err14>The second argument must be a rounding convention ("z" for the AwayFromZero convention or "e" for the ToEven convention) or the number of fractional digits</err14>
    <err15>Function must contain no more than three arguments</err15>
    <err16>Function must contain two numeric arguments separated by a comma</err16>
    <err17>Function must contain three comma-separated arguments: a condition, a value when the condition is met, and a value when the condition is not met</err17>
    <err18>Function must contain at least two conditions separated by a comma</err18>
    <err19>Function must contain two comma-separated arguments: the number to be checked and the range of numbers separated by two dots ".."</err19>
    <err20>Argument "{0}" must contain two numbers separated by two dots ".."</err20>
    <err21>Function must contain at least two arguments separated by semicolons</err21>
    <err22>Argument "{0}" must contain a condition and a value, separated by a colon</err22>
    <err23>Failed to convert value "{0}" to a number</err23>
    <err24>Failed calculate function</err24>
    <err25>Sheet "{0}" contains the wrong number of rows and columns</err25>
    <err26>Column 4 of row 1 on the "{0}" sheet should contain a unique strategy identifier (Self, OnlyFamilies, Types, InHost, etc.)</err26>
    <err27>Error when reading categories</err27>
    <err28>Error when reading parameters</err28>
    <err29>Invalid formula</err29>
    <err30>Row processing failed with error</err30>
    <err31>Unsupported type of strategy</err31>
    <err32>error of the expression "{0}"</err32>
    <err33>parameter "{0}" is not found</err33>
    <err34>Revit could not set a value in the parameter</err34>
    <!-- todo remove after 2.31.10.0 -->
    <err35>unsupported reference value type of parameter</err35>
    <err36>reference value "{0}" when set to "{1}" is not found</err36>
    <err37>parameter "{0}" is not available for editing</err37>
    <err38>parameter "{0}" has data type "Integer", but set value "{1}" is not an integer</err38>
    <err39>the parent strategy does not allow using parameters of conditional source elements (@[Parameter])</err39>
    <err40>failed to get the field from the value "{0}". The value must begin with a field key enclosed in angle brackets</err40>
    <err41>the parameter "{0}" has no data type defined</err41>
    <err42>the empty value obtained when calculating the formula is not written to the parameter, because the "Write empty" option is not enabled in the formula</err42>
    <err43>type with the name "{0}" is not found in the list of allowable types of the element to be processed</err43>
    <err44>type with name "{0}" already exists</err44>
    <err45>Element identifier (ID) cannot be used as the target parameter</err45>
    <err46>The second argument must be an integer greater than zero</err46>
    <err48>The third argument must be a positive integer greater than zero</err48>
    <err49>Function must contain two arguments</err49>
    <err50>Function must contain two or three arguments</err50>
    <err51>The field with the key "{0}" is already in the list of fields of the current formula</err51>
    <err52>Parameter "{0}" is not a reference to another model element</err52>
    <err53>The target parameter must not contain the character "|"</err53>
    <err54>An expression must not contain parentheses that are not function boundaries. To add parentheses to an expression, they must be escaped – "\)" and "\("</err54>
    <err55>Function must contain a pointer to a parameter (@[] or $[]) as an argument</err55>
    <err56>The list contains fields with the same key!</err56>
    <err57>A workset named "{0}" was not found</err57>
    <err58>Function must not have any arguments</err58>
    <err59>Function must contain three arguments: source value, value to search and value to replace</err59>
    <err60>The unique strategy identifier "{0}" on sheet "{1}" does not match the current strategy identifier "{2}"</err60>
    <err61>Function must contain the address of the cell, of the form "A1"</err61>
    <err62>Data source Excel-file not specified or not found</err62>
    <err63>Insulation type "{0}" is not found in the current project</err63>
    <err64>The "ToRoom" and "FromRoom" key parameters may only be used when processing families in the "Doors", "Windows" categories</err64>
    <err65>No source element matching the filtering conditions was found in the model</err65>
    <err66>The data for assigning the result of an expression calculation is not defined</err66>
    <err67>Each expression in the formula must begin with the target parameter "$[Parameter Name]=", or with the function of writing the join of results to the conditional source element "JOIN(@[Parameter Name],)=", or with the function of writing the sum of results to the conditional source element "SUM(@[Parameter Name])="</err67>
    <err68>Failed to retrieve a number from the value "{0}"</err68>
    <err69>Unable to write the result to a conditional source element from a linked file</err69>
    <err70>Element is occupied by user "{0}" and is not available for modification</err70>
    <err71>No source element matching the filtering conditions was found on the current view</err71>
    <err72>Unable to write result to parameter of element from linked file</err72>
    <err73>Function must contain at least two arguments: a condition and a pointer to the result column</err73>
    <err74>The name of column {0} must be specified by a Latin letter or number</err74>
    <rh1>#</rh1>
    <rh2>On</rh2>
    <rh3>Formula</rh3>
    <rh4>Formula options</rh4>
    <sm1>Process picked elements</sm1>
    <sm2>Process elements on current View</sm2>
    <sm3>Process elements in Document</sm3>
    <sm4>Process elements on selected views</sm4>
    <ssd1>Processing elements without relationships</ssd1>
    <sld1>Strategy processes elements without considering their relationships to other elements. At least one filter (by category or by parameter) must be filled</sld1>
    <ssd2>Processing family instances without relationships</ssd2>
    <sld2>Strategy processes instances of families without considering their relationships to other elements. It is acceptable not to use a filter by category or filter by parameter</sld2>
    <ssd3>Processing types</ssd3>
    <sld3>Strategy processes types. If the "Process picked elements" option is selected, then the types of the selected elements will be processed. If the "Process elements on current View" option is selected, then the types of elements on the current View will be processed. If the "Process elements in the document" option is selected then all types in the document are processed</sld3>
    <ssd4>Processing elements in the Host</ssd4>
    <sld4>Strategy processes elements that have information about the Hosts. Such elements include: Rebar, Area Reinforcement, Path Reinforcement, Rebar Container, Openings, Stacked Walls, and Families (including elements of Curtain Walls)</sld4>
    <ssd5>Processing elements in the Group</ssd5>
    <sld5>Strategy processes elements placed in groups. When creating formulas, keep in mind that the target parameter must be able to change across group instances</sld5>
    <ssd6>Processing elements in the Room</ssd6>
    <sld6>Strategy processes elements located in Rooms</sld6>
    <ssd7>Processing elements in the Space</ssd7>
    <sld7>Strategy processes elements located in Spaces</sld7>
    <ssd8>Processing elements in the Mass</ssd8>
    <sld8>Strategy processes elements that have Solid geometry and are located in Masses. Masses must have a Solid form</sld8>
    <ssd9>Processing elements in the Solid</ssd9>
    <sld9>Strategy processes elements that have Solid geometry and are located inside other elements that have Solid geometry</sld9>
    <ssd10>Processing elements that touch their solids</ssd10>
    <sld10>Strategy processes elements that Solid geometry and have flat solid faces that touch each other</sld10>
    <ssd11>Processing room boundaries</ssd11>
    <sld11>Strategy processes elements that are room boundaries</sld11>
    <ssd12>Processing sub-elements of Structure Connections</ssd12>
    <sld12>Strategy processes elements placed in Structure Connections (Plates, bolts, etc.). Filtering of sub-elements by parameters, as well as the list of parameters of sub-elements in the formula editor, are not provided. Numerical parameters are set without conversion to internal units</sld12>
    <ssd13>Processing nested families</ssd13>
    <sld13>Strategy processes families that are nested within the parent family</sld13>
    <ssd14>Pipe and Duct Insulation processing</ssd14>
    <sld14>Processing Pipe insulation elements and/or Duct insulation elements. It is acceptable not to use a parameter filter for insulation</sld14>
    <ssd15>Processing of rebars in the system</ssd15>
    <sld15>Strategy processes rebars as part of reinforcement systems – Area reinforcement and Path reinforcement</sld15>
    <ssd16>Processing materials</ssd16>
    <sld16>Strategy processes all materials of the current document regardless of the element selection option</sld16>
    <ssd17>Processing elements of MEP systems</ssd17>
    <sld17>Strategy processes elements that are part of an MEP system (electrical system, piping system or duct system). Conditional source element is the element's parent system</sld17>
    <ssd18>Processing of Curtain Wall components</ssd18>
    <sld18>Strategy processes the components of the Curtain Wall (imposts and panels). Conditional source element is the wall</sld18>
    <ssd19>Processing of elements in relation to specified source elements</ssd19>
    <sld19>Strategy processes elements with the possibility to use any specified element of the model as a source element</sld19>
    <ssd20>Processing Parts</ssd20>
    <sld20>Strategy processes Parts taking into account the source elements from which the Parts are created. If a part is created from several source elements, the first element will be considered the source element</sld20>
    <se1>Host</se1>
    <sp1>Insert Host parameter</sp1>
    <se2>Group</se2>
    <sp2>Insert Group parameter</sp2>
    <se3>Room</se3>
    <sp3>Insert Room parameter</sp3>
    <se4>Space</se4>
    <sp4>Insert Space parameter</sp4>
    <se5>Mass</se5>
    <sp5>Insert Mass parameter</sp5>
    <se6>Parent element</se6>
    <sp6>Insert parameter of parent element</sp6>
    <se7>Touchable element</se7>
    <sp7>Insert parameter of touchable element</sp7>
    <se8>Connection</se8>
    <sp8>Insert parameter of Structural Connection</sp8>
    <se9>Parent family</se9>
    <sp9>Insert parameter of parent family</sp9>
    <se10>Pipe or Duct</se10>
    <sp10>Insert Pipe or Duct parameter</sp10>
    <se11>System</se11>
    <sp11>Insert parent reinforcement system parameter</sp11>
    <se12>MEP system</se12>
    <sp12>Insert parent MEP system parameter</sp12>
    <se13>Curtain Wall</se13>
    <sp13>Insert Curtain Wall parameter</sp13>
    <se14>Source element</se14>
    <sp14>Insert source element parameter</sp14>
    <te1>Target element</te1>
    <tp1>Insert parameter of target element</tp1>
    <te2>Family instance</te2>
    <tp2>Insert parameter of target family instance</tp2>
    <te3>Type</te3>
    <tp3>Insert parameter of target Type</tp3>
    <te4>SubElement</te4>
    <tp4>Insert target Sub-element parameter</tp4>
    <te5>Nested family</te5>
    <tp5>Insert nested family parameter</tp5>
    <te6>Insulation</te6>
    <tp6>Insert insulation parameter</tp6>
    <te7>Rebar</te7>
    <tp7>Insert target rebar parameter</tp7>
    <te8>Material</te8>
    <tp8>Insert material parameter</tp8>
    <te9>Part</te9>
    <tp10>Insert part parameter</tp10>
    <ft1>Mathematical functions</ft1>
    <ft2>Logical functions</ft2>
    <ft3>Modifying functions</ft3>
    <ft4>Value retrieval functions</ft4>
    <d-min>Returns the smaller of numbers</d-min>
    <d-max>Returns the larger of numbers</d-max>
    <d-abs>Returns the absolute value of the number</d-abs>
    <d-round>Rounds a value to the nearest integer or to the specified number of fractional digits</d-round>
    <d-roundup>Returns the smallest integral value greater than or equal to the specified number</d-roundup>
    <d-rounddown>Returns the largest integral value less than or equal to the specified number</d-rounddown>
    <d-sqrt>Returns the square root of a specified number</d-sqrt>
    <d-pow>Returns a specified number raised to the specified power</d-pow>
    <d-sin>Returns the sine of a specified angle</d-sin>
    <d-cos>Returns the cosine of a specified angle</d-cos>
    <d-tan>Returns the tangent of a specified angle</d-tan>
    <d-asin>Returns the angle whose sine is the specified number</d-asin>
    <d-acos>Returns the angle whose cosine is the specified number</d-acos>
    <d-atan>Returns the angle whose tangent is the specified number</d-atan>
    <d-log>Returns the logarithm of a specified number with a specified base</d-log>
    <d-ln>Returns the natural logarithm (with base e) of the specified number</d-ln>
    <d-exp>Returns e multiplied by the specified power</d-exp>
    <d-pi>Returns the ratio of the circumference of a circle to its diameter</d-pi>
    <d-if>Returns the first value &lt;true&gt; if the condition &lt;c&gt; is true. Returns the second value &lt;false&gt; if the condition &lt;c&gt; is not true</d-if>
    <d-and>Returns TRUE if all conditions &lt;c&gt; are true. Otherwise returns FALSE</d-and>
    <d-or>Returns TRUE if at least one condition &lt;c&gt; is true. Otherwise returns FALSE</d-or>
    <d-inrange>Returns TRUE if the number &lt;x&gt; is greater than or equal to &lt;min&gt; and less than or equal to &lt;max&gt;. Otherwise returns FALSE</d-inrange>
    <d-has>Returns TRUE if parameter &lt;p&gt; exists. Otherwise returns FALSE</d-has>
    <d-firsttrue>Returns the first value of &lt;v&gt; whose &lt;c&gt; condition is true. If all conditions &lt;c&gt; are not true, returns last &lt;v&gt; value</d-firsttrue>
    <d-toupper>Returns value converted to uppercase</d-toupper>
    <d-tolower>Returns value converted to lowercase</d-tolower>
    <d-lstr>Returns the specified number of characters from the start of the string</d-lstr>
    <d-rstr>Returns the specified number of characters from the end of the string</d-rstr>
    <d-sstr>Returns substring</d-sstr>
    <d-tmirrored>Returns TRUE if the target family is mirrored</d-tmirrored>
    <d-smirrored>Returns TRUE if the conditional source family is mirrored</d-smirrored>
    <d-strlen>Returns string length</d-strlen>
    <d-strindex>Returns an index counting from zero of the first occurrence of the substring in the string. Returns -1 if the substring is not found in the string</d-strindex>
    <d-valuestr>Returns the value of the parameter as a string with units</d-valuestr>
    <d-eindex>Returns the index of the successful use of the current formula expression</d-eindex>
    <d-replace>Returns value in which all occurrences of the given string are replaced by another given string</d-replace>
    <d-format>Converts a number to a string using the specified format</d-format>
    <d-cv>Returns the value from the specified cell of the strategy data source</d-cv>
    <d-count>Returns the number of times the substring occurs in the string. If the substring is not found in the string, returns 0</d-count>
    <d-lstrindex>Returns an index counting from zero of the last occurrence of the substring in the string. Returns -1 if the substring is not found in the string</d-lstrindex>
    <d-not>Returns TRUE if the condition is false. Otherwise returns FALSE</d-not>
    <d-distinct>Returns the differing values of the list, ignoring the start and end spaces when comparing values</d-distinct>
    <d-cvif>Looks for the first row in the strategy data source (Excel file) where all conditions are met and returns the value from the specified column of that row</d-cvif>
  </mprParametrization>
</ModPlus>