<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModPlus>
  <mprParameters
    LocalName="Parameters"
    Description="Batch editing/adding parameters to projects and families"
    LocalName1="Family Editor"
    Description1="Analog of the standard parameter editor of the current family, allowing to use an alternative formula editor">
    <pcn1>Create parameters in project</pcn1>
    <pcd1>Allows batch creation of parameters in the current project</pcd1>
    <pcn2>Create parameters in families</pcn2>
    <pcd2>Allows batch creation of parameters in project families, open families, or families on disk</pcd2>
    <!-- todo remove after 1.6.2.0 -->
    <pcn3>Family Editor</pcn3>
    <!-- todo remove after 1.6.2.0 -->
    <pcd3>Analog of the standard parameter editor of the current family, allowing to use an alternative formula editor</pcd3>
    <pcn4>Edit parameters in project</pcn4>
    <pcd4>Allows batch editing of parameters in the current project</pcd4>
    <pcn5>Edit parameters in families</pcn5>
    <pcd5>Allows batch editing of parameters in project families, open families, or families on disk</pcd5>
    <t1>No document</t1>
    <t2>Family</t2>
    <t3>Project</t3>
    <t4>Formula validation is performed by the family {0}</t4>
    <t5>The formula editor is opened based on the {0} family data. The formula is not validated</t5>
    <t6>Closing family {0}</t6>
    <t7>Families with parameter "{0}"</t7>
    <t8>Select parameters</t8>
    <t9>Change formula</t9>
    <t10>Change group</t10>
    <t11>Change behavior</t11>
    <t12>Values can vary by group instance</t12>
    <t13>Values are aligned per group type</t13>
    <!--todo remove after 1.6.2.0-->
    <t14>Make "By instance"</t14>
    <!--todo remove after 1.6.2.0-->
    <t15>Make "By Type"</t15>
    <t16>Rename</t16>
    <t17>Parameter exists in the current document</t17>
    <t18>New parameter</t18>
    <t19>By instance</t19>
    <t20>Shared parameter</t20>
    <t21>Built-in parameter</t21>
    <t22>Family parameter</t22>
    <t23>Families</t23>
    <t24>*DIFFERENT*</t24>
    <t25>Data type not defined</t25>
    <t26>Project parameter</t26>
    <t27>By type</t27>
    <t28>Check parameter properties</t28>
    <t29>Other</t29>
    <t30>SPF Group</t30>
    <t31>Data Type</t31>
    <t32>Group parameter under</t32>
    <t33>Family processing</t33>
    <t34>Adding parameter</t34>
    <t35>Setting parameter values...</t35>
    <t36>Setting formula values...</t36>
    <t37>Adding parameters</t37>
    <t38>Parameter created</t38>
    <t39>Parameter updated</t39>
    <t40>Parameter update skipped</t40>
    <t41>Enter new name</t41>
    <t42>Select new group</t42>
    <t43>Enter type name</t43>
    <t44>Parameter processing</t44>
    <t45>Family reading</t45>
    <t46>Obtaining parameter data</t46>
    <t47>Batch editing of parameters</t47>
    <t48>Update project parameter</t48>
    <t49>Create project parameter</t49>
    <t50>Setting standard values</t50>
    <t51>Name</t51>
    <t52>Instance/Type</t52>
    <t53>Values by groups</t53>
    <t54>Default value</t54>
    <t55>Categories</t55>
    <t56>Project parameters</t56>
    <t57>Family parameters</t57>
    <t58>Select the path to save the file</t58>
    <t59>Change current type</t59>
    <t60>Create type</t60>
    <t61>Remove type</t61>
    <t62>Rename type</t62>
    <t63>Remove parameter</t63>
    <t64>Replace parameter</t64>
    <t65>Set formula</t65>
    <t66>Set parameter value</t66>
    <t67>Change parameter lock</t67>
    <t68>Change "Instance/Type" property</t68>
    <t69>Create parameter</t69>
    <t70>Custom parameter</t70>
    <t71>Shared Parameters File</t71>
    <t72>Action after exporting to Excel:</t72>
    <t73>Action when parameter exists:</t73>
    <t74>Retrieve data</t74>
    <t75>From files</t75>
    <t76>From folder</t76>
    <t77>Processed families</t77>
    <t78>Remove all families from the list</t78>
    <t79>Insert parameter</t79>
    <t80>Insert function</t80>
    <t81>Select all or deselect</t81>
    <t82>Select SPF:</t82>
    <t83>Current SPF</t83>
    <t84>Selected SPF</t84>
    <t85>Path to SPF:</t85>
    <t86>Add from SPF</t86>
    <t87>Add selected parameters from the SPF to the current parameter list</t87>
    <t88>Groups</t88>
    <t89>Parameter definitions</t89>
    <t90>Total parameters:</t90>
    <t91>Selected parameters:</t91>
    <t92>Create family parameter</t92>
    <t93>Export parameter list to Excel</t93>
    <t94>Import parameter list from Excel</t94>
    <t95>Remove selected parameters from the list</t95>
    <t96>Remove all parameters from the list</t96>
    <t97>Create</t97>
    <!--todo remove after 1.6.2.0-->
    <t98>Instance</t98>
    <!--todo remove after 1.6.2.0-->
    <t99>Type</t99>
    <t100>Formula Editor</t100>
    <t101>Execute and close</t101>
    <t102>Edit the list of categories of the selected parameters</t102>
    <t103>Create a custom parameter. The custom parameter will be a Shared parameter with a random GUID, but with no binding to a specific SPF</t103>
    <t104>State</t104>
    <t105>Not supported</t105>
    <t106>Type name:</t106>
    <t107>Create new type</t107>
    <t108>Remove current type</t108>
    <t109>Replace the shared parameter with a family parameter</t109>
    <t110>Lock</t110>
    <t111>Not available</t111>
    <t112>Make parameter of instance</t112>
    <t113>Make parameter of type</t113>
    <t114>Clear the list of actions</t114>
    <t115>Count</t115>
    <t116>Count of families with this parameter</t116>
    <t117>Actions</t117>
    <t118>Change by group</t118>
    <t119>Change by instance</t119>
    <!-- todo remove after 1.6.2.0 -->
    <t120>Values by group</t120>
    <t121>Validate</t121>
    <t122>Accept without validation</t122>
    <t123>Add the current formula to the favorites list</t123>
    <t124>Insert a formula from the favorites list</t124>
    <t125>Section</t125>
    <t126>Current document type:</t126>
    <t127>Available sections:</t127>
    <t128>Unavailable sections:</t128>
    <t129>{0} categories</t129>
    <t130>Trial Period. Days left</t130>
    <t131>The plugin's trial period is over! Purchase a plugin license or Revit subscription to continue using the "Parameters" plugin</t131>
    <t132>Favorite formulas</t132>
    <t133>Ignore nested families</t133>
    <t134>Other</t134>
    <t135>On plugin startup, open a section in the family document:</t135>
    <t136>Case sensitive searches in the list of data types, parameter groups, column filters and the dialog box for adding parameters from the SPF</t136>
    <!-- todo remove after 1.6.2.0 -->
    <t137>Change group</t137>
    <t138>Select a new group for the parameter "{0}"</t138>
    <t139>Select families</t139>
    <t140>Delete backup files</t140>
    <t141>After saving the family, all backup files of the form Family_name.nnnn.rfa next to the family file will be deleted</t141>
    <t142>Due to limitations in Revit API, if you change the group of a non-shared family parameter, the description will be lost!</t142>
    <t143>In the current family type, it is not possible to use the plugin. The family editor is open in Read Only mode</t143>
    <t144>The row corresponding to the parameter is not found in the imported file</t144>
    <t145>Failed to recognize the action in "{0}". Make sure that the application language matches the file being loaded</t145>
    <t146>An action from the value "{0}" is recognized but not added to the parameter "{1}" because the action is not applicable to the parameter or the parameter is already marked as deletable</t146>
    <t147>Failed to recognize the group specified in "{0}". Some group names may differ between Revit versions</t147>
    <t148>You do not have access to save presets to the organization's preset storage</t148>
    <t149>Load preset</t149>
    <t150>Save preset</t150>
    <t151>Preset name</t151>
    <t152>There are no saved presets for the current section in the storage</t152>
    <t153>Change parameter definition</t153>
    <t154>Add categories</t154>
    <t155>Remove categories</t155>
    <t156>Add an action to the selected parameters</t156>
    <t157>Select an action</t157>
    <t158>Not bound to project categories</t158>
    <t159>Change the binding to categories</t159>
    <t160>Save to:</t160>
    <t161>User storage</t161>
    <t162>Organization storage</t162>
    <t163>Remove unused parameters</t163>
    <t164>Remove checked parameters</t164>
    <t165>Used</t165>
    <t166>Built-in parameter cannot be removed</t166>
    <t167>Used in the "{0}" parameter formula</t167>
    <t168>Used in dimension (ID={0})</t168>
    <t169>Used in an array (ID={0})</t169>
    <t170>Associated with the "{0}" parameter of element ID={1}</t170>
    <t171>ToolTip</t171>
    <t172>Set ToolTip</t172>
    <t173>Revit API does not allow to retrieve an existing parameter ToolTip</t173>
    <t174>Replace the family parameter with a shared parameter</t174>
    <t175>Select parameter</t175>
    <t176>Replace the shared parameter with another shared parameter</t176>
    <t177>Duplicate parameter</t177>
    <t178>Change the order of parameters</t178>
    <t179>Drag the parameters in the table to set their new position. It is allowed to drag multiple parameters, as well as to drag parameters to other groups</t179>
    <t180>Due to limitations in the Revit API, system parameters cannot be moved to other groups</t180>
    <t181>Family files</t181>
    <t182>Import parameters from the selected family</t182>
    <t183>Import parameters</t183>
    <t184>Number of imported parameters</t184>
    <t185>Current family</t185>
    <t186>Selected family</t186>
    <t187>Import of parameters is performed by creating parameters in the current family with the characteristics of the selected parameters of the selected family and then setting the values ​​and formulas. When selecting a parameter with a formula, all parameters used in the formula will be added to the list. Import of system parameters is not possible. In the left part of the window, you must select the ratio of the types of the current and selected families, according to which the parameter values ​​will be copied</t187>
    <t188>Due to limitations in the Revit API, parameter imports lose parameter descriptions unless the selected shared parameter is present in the current shared parameter file</t188>
    <t189>Import formula</t189>
    <t190>Import a formula from a parameter of the selected family</t190>
    <t191>There are no parameters with formulas in the selected family</t191>
    <ad1>Allows you to rename a family parameter. The action is not available for system parameters and shared parameters</ad1>
    <ad2>Allows you to change the group of the parameter. The action is not available for system parameters. If you change the group of a non-shared parameter of a family, the description will be lost</ad2>
    <ad3>Allows you to change the group of the parameter. The action is not available for project parameters</ad3>
    <ad4>Allows you to add or remove the binding of shared parameter to categories. The action is not available for project parameters. If you delete a binding to categories, all parameter data will be removed from the elements of these categories</ad4>
    <ad6>Allows you to make a family parameter an instance parameter. The action is not available for system parameters</ad6>
    <ad7>Allows you to make a shared parameter an instance parameter. The action is not available for project parameters</ad7>
    <ad8>Allows you to make a family parameter a type parameter. The action is not available for system parameters</ad8>
    <ad9>Allows you to make a shared parameter a type parameter. The action is not available for project parameters</ad9>
    <ad10>Allows you to set the "Values can vary by group instance" behavior for parameters</ad10>
    <ad11>Allows you to set the "Values are aligned per group type" behavior for parameters</ad11>
    <ad12>Allows you to delete the parameter. Action is not available for system parameters</ad12>
    <ad13>Allows you to delete the parameter</ad13>
    <ad14>Allows you to replace a shared parameter with a family parameter while preserving the parameter name</ad14>
    <ea1>Nothing</ea1>
    <ea2>Open target folder</ea2>
    <ea3>Open created file</ea3>
    <ea4>Ask for opening target folder</ea4>
    <ep1>Skip</ep1>
    <ep2>Set formula (if possible)</ep2>
    <ep3>Set value (if possible)</ep3>
    <ep4>Set formula or value (if possible)</ep4>
    <fs1>From file</fs1>
    <fs2>From project</fs2>
    <fs3>Open families</fs3>
    <fs4>From Project Browser</fs4>
    <s1>Selected elements</s1>
    <s2>On active view</s2>
    <s3>In project</s3>
    <d1>Common</d1>
    <d2>Electrical</d2>
    <d3>Energy</d3>
    <d4>HVAC</d4>
    <d5>Piping</d5>
    <d6>Structural</d6>
    <d7>Infrastructure</d7>
    <spf1>Parameter not found in the specified shared parameters file</spf1>
    <spf2>Parameter found in the specified shared parameter file</spf2>
    <spf3>A parameter with the same name but a different GUID was found in the specified shared parameters file</spf3>
    <spf4>A parameter with the same GUID but a different name was found in the specified shared parameters file</spf4>
    <spf5>Unable to search for a parameter in a shared parameter file because no shared parameter file is specified</spf5>
    <msg1>The formula has been added to the favorites list</msg1>
    <msg2>The current formula is not empty. Are you sure to replace it with a formula from the favorites list?</msg2>
    <msg3>Shared parameter is already present in the current parameter list</msg3>
    <msg4>A parameter with this name, data type and grouping is already present in the current parameter list</msg4>
    <msg5>All selected parameters cannot be renamed</msg5>
    <msg6>The type named "{0}" already exists</msg6>
    <msg7>Are you sure you want to remove the type "{0}"?</msg7>
    <msg8>Remove the "{0}" parameter?</msg8>
    <msg9>Remove selected parameters ({0})?</msg9>
    <msg10>The parameter creation is skipped, because the family already has such a parameter</msg10>
    <msg12>The parameter has not been created</msg12>
    <msg13>The value of the parameter is set</msg13>
    <msg14>Failed to set the parameter value</msg14>
    <msg15>Parameter formula updated</msg15>
    <msg16>Failed to update the parameter formula</msg16>
    <msg17>Parameter removed</msg17>
    <msg18>Parameter renamed</msg18>
    <msg19>The value "{0}" is set</msg19>
    <msg20>Unknown action</msg20>
    <msg21>Parameter "{0}" has been deleted</msg21>
    <msg22>The formula has been changed</msg22>
    <msg23>Parameter made "By instance"</msg23>
    <msg24>Parameter made "By type"</msg24>
    <msg25>Parameter moved to group "{0}"</msg25>
    <msg26>Open the export folder?</msg26>
    <msg27>Process families from nested directories?</msg27>
    <msg28>The formula editor will be opened without the ability to validate the formula</msg28>
    <msg29>No Shared Parameter File has been set in the current project</msg29>
    <!--todo remove after 1.6.2.0-->
    <msg30>Check if the parameter name and type values are filled in</msg30>
    <msg31>Check if the parameter name, type, group and category list values are filled in</msg31>
    <msg32>The entered value does not match the parameter type</msg32>
    <msg33>The Revit API does not allow to create or edit parameters in families of some types. Loading such families is skipped</msg33>
    <msg34>Preset "{0}" will be irrevocably deleted! Continue?</msg34>
    <msg35>Preset "{0}" has been deleted</msg35>
    <msg36>Shared parameter replaced by Family parameter</msg36>
    <msg37>The parameter is bound to categories:</msg37>
    <msg38>The parameter is unbound from the categories:</msg38>
    <msg39>The plugin is only available in the family document!</msg39>
    <err1>An unexpected error occurred during window initialization</err1>
    <err2>An unexpected error occurred when closing the window</err2>
    <err3>An error occurred while creating the parameter</err3>
    <err4>Failed to add parameter binding</err4>
    <err5>Failed to get parameter binding</err5>
    <err6>Failed to update parameter binding</err6>
    <err7>Failed to execute actions</err7>
    <err8>Failed to execute action with parameter "{0}"</err8>
    <err9>Parameter with GUID "{0}" is omitted because no SPF is specified</err9>
    <err10>Parameter with GUID "{0}" is not found in the current SPF</err10>
    <err11>Not recognized data type "{0}" for parameter</err11>
    <err12>Not recognized group "{0}" for parameter</err12>
    <err13>Not recognized category for parameter "{0}"</err13>
    <err14>Failed to read row</err14>
    <err15>The family has been saved in a later version of Revit</err15>
    <err16>Unable to set the value "{0}" to an integer parameter</err16>
    <err17>Unsupported data type "{0}"</err17>
    <err18>Instance Parameters can't be used in Type Parameter formulas</err18>
    <err19>Failed to set the formula</err19>
    <err20>Failed to create parameter "{0}" in family "{1}"</err20>
    <err21>The family is not loaded because the family file has a "Read Only" attribute</err21>
    <err22>Failed to set a formula to a parameter because an uncontrolled error occurred in the Revit API, indicating a bug in the Revit API. To set a formula to this parameter, use the standard parameter editing dialog</err22>
    <err23>Specify the name of the preset</err23>
    <err24>There is already a preset with this name in the storage. The existing preset will be overwritten!</err24>
    <err25>The preset name must not contain the following characters: \ / : * ? " &lt; &gt; |</err25>
    <err26>Preset storage directory is missing! Make sure you have access to create folders and files in the UserData directory or contact your system administrator</err26>
    <err27>Failed to execute action</err27>
    <err28>A parameter named "{0}" has already been defined. Set another name</err28>
    <err29>The selected family is the current family. Select another family</err29>
    <err30>Failed to import parameters. Error:</err30>
    <err31>Failed to set the formula. Error:</err31>
    <err32>The parameter value cannot be imported</err32>
    <err33>Failed to undo the changes made because the current document is not a document of the edited family. Switch to the family document and undo the changes manually</err33>
    <err34>A parameter with the data type "Image" cannot be an instance parameter</err34>
    <err35>Parameter name not specified</err35>
    <err36>Parameter data type not specified</err36>
    <err37>Parameter binding categories not specified</err37>
    <err38>Parameter group not specified</err38>
  </mprParameters>
</ModPlus>