<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModPlus>
  <mprNumbering
    LocalName="Numbering"
    Description="Adding numbering to the specified parameter of elements with the possibility of numbering in the schedules"
    FullDescription="When working in a non-schedule view, you can specify the direction of numbering based on the arrangement of elements, or add numbering in the order in which elements were created. When working in a schedule, the plugin adds numbering in the order of items in the schedule (taking into account sorting). It is possible to set the prefix and suffix for the number">
    <h7>Initial value:</h7>
    <h8>Numbering direction:</h8>
    <h9>Target parameter:</h9>
    <h12>Instance parameter</h12>
    <h13>Type parameter</h13>
    <h14>Parameter</h14>
    <h15>has the "Read Only" property for the following elements</h15>
    <h16>It is not possible to change the instance parameter for an element located in a group if the parameter "Values can vary by group instances" is not enabled for the parameter or it is not the "Mark" system parameter</h16>
    <h17>Errors occurred while changing the parameter values of the listed items</h17>
    <h18>Attention! The parameter is cleared for all elements of this schedule, regardless of the filtering settings. This means that if, for example, 10 columns are presented in the schedule, and only 5 columns are displayed in the filter settings, then the parameter will be cleared for all 10 columns! Clear parameter?</h18>
    <h20>Selection variant:</h20>
    <h21>Selected elements count:</h21>
    <h24>Number only selected rows</h24>
    <h25>Elements selection</h25>
    <h26>Numbering settings</h26>
    <h27>Step:</h27>
    <h28>The "{0}" parameter has a "Read-only" property. Make sure that the elements to be processed are not in a Workset that is not available to you for editing</h28>
    <h29>Prefix and suffix from</h29>
    <h30>string</h30>
    <h31>parameter</h31>
    <h32>Create a new configuration</h32>
    <h33>Rename the configuration</h33>
    <h34>Enter a new configuration name</h34>
    <h35>Remove configuration</h35>
    <h36>Numeric parameter</h36>
    <h37>String parameter</h37>
    <h38>Alphabet:</h38>
    <h39>Custom</h39>
    <h40>Russian</h40>
    <h41>English</h41>
    <h42>Ukrainian</h42>
    <h43>Enter the letters of the alphabet without spaces in any case. You can also</h43>
    <h44>insert</h44>
    <h45>and edit</h45>
    <h46>alphabet</h46>
    <h47>Custom alphabet</h47>
    <h48>Grouping by parameter:</h48>
    <h49>Group behavior:</h49>
    <sv1>Standard frame selection</sv1>
    <sv2>Ordinal selection</sv2>
    <sv3>Curve intersection</sv3>
    <!-- todo remove after 6.1.2.0 -->
    <select>Select</select>
    <t1>The work of the plugin is possible only in the schedule in the sorting settings of which the property "Itemize every instance" is checked</t1>
    <t2>Uncheck all categories</t2>
    <t3>Standard frame selection – selection of elements in the current view with a frame with confirmation of the selection by pressing the "Finish" button. With this option, the numbering direction has nine options – in the order of creation and by the position of the elements.</t3>
    <t4>Ordinal selection – selects each element for numbering in the order in which the numbering will be performed. With this option, the direction of numbering can be ascending or descending. Completion of the selection is invoked by pressing the Esc key.</t4>
    <t5>Curve intersection – Select a curve (model line or detail line). The elements for numbering will be selected by finding the intersection of the curve with the geometry of the elements in the current view, projected onto the plane of the view. With this option, the direction of numbering can be ascending or descending.</t5>
    <t6>It is possible to apply a filter by category and/or parameters to all element selections.</t6>
    <t7>The list of parameters is filled in after selecting the elements for numbering.</t7>
    <t12>The initial value can be a fractional value. A point or comma can be used to separate the integer part from the fractional part. The specified separator will be used when setting values in the text parameter. If the target parameter is of data type "Number", the specified separator will not affect the displayed result. If the target parameter is of data type "Integer", the numbering result will be converted to an integer by discarding the fractional part.</t12>
    <t13>Leading zeros can be added to the initial value. For example, if the initial value is "01", and the step is "5", then the numbering result will be "01, 05, 10, 15...". Initial zeros are only taken into account if the target parameter has a string data type.</t13>
    <!-- todo remove after 5.2.16.0 -->
    <t14>The geometric direction of numbering is calculated by the absolute values of X and Y of the element placement points. For linear objects the middle point is taken</t14>
    <t15>When sorting linear objects, the center point is used. When sorting viewports, the center of the viewport is used. When sorting tags, the header placement point is used. In other cases, the insertion point of the element is used</t15>
    <t16>You can apply letter numbering. To do this, specify the letter of the alphabet from which the alphabetic numbering will start as the initial value. Alphabetic numbering will be performed in the same case in which the initial value is specified.</t16>
    <m1>Select elements for numbered marking</m1>
    <m2>No items on current view schedule</m2>
    <m3>Filter selected elements by the current list of categories?</m3>
    <m4>Select a curve (model line or detail line)</m4>
    <o1>Ascending</o1>
    <o2>Descending</o2>
    <b1>Numbering in each group</b1>
    <b2>One number per group</b2>
    <b3>Through numbering with sorting by parameter (ascending)</b3>
    <b4>Through numbering with sorting by parameter (descending)</b4>
    <d1>In ascending order of creation</d1>
    <d1-1>In descending order of creation</d1-1>
    <d2>Left to right and top to bottom</d2>
    <d3>Left to right and bottom to top</d3>
    <d4>Right to left and top to bottom</d4>
    <d5>Right to left and bottom to top</d5>
    <d6>Top to bottom and left to right</d6>
    <d7>Top to bottom and right to left</d7>
    <d8>Bottom to top and left to right</d8>
    <d9>Bottom to top and right to left</d9>
    <d10>Left to right</d10>
    <d11>Right to left</d11>
    <d12>Top to bottom</d12>
    <d13>Bottom to top</d13>
    <r1>Initial value not set</r1>
    <r2>No elements selected for processing</r2>
    <r3>Empty custom alphabet</r3>
    <r4>The letter "{0}" is not in the selected alphabet</r4>
    <r5>Letter numbering cannot be performed because the numeric parameter is selected</r5>
    <r6>Parameter for grouping not selected</r6>
  </mprNumbering>
</ModPlus>